netakart.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy - Netakart.com

#### Principles

We value your privacy, this Privacy Policy is meant to protect your personal information and keep it confidential. We comply with the laws of the land and do everything we can to protect your rights of privacy on our website and systems. However, we are not liable for any unauthorised/illegal disclosures of your personal/confidential information made by third parties such as advertisers, business partners and websites that have links to our Website. This privacy policy may change at some point, to be aware of the changes, please review this policy periodically. 

#### Definition

Personal information is: a) Personal identity information you enter into our system while creating your profile such as: gender, marital status, age, preferences, phone numbers, fax numbers, mail ids, your social website contacts, likes and dislikes. It also includes your user account information such as usernames, passwords and other security related information. b) Billing information you have with us such as bank account details, payment history and order/return/exchange communications. c) Website usage information such as urls from where you landed on our website, login time, IP address, cookies, browser types and time of web requests. It also includes the data created on our website by you such as pictures and documents.

We don't sell or trade your confidential/personal information with anybody. All your sensitive user data related to your login account are encrypted. If we need to use your personal information, we'll request your written consent. If you decline it we won't use it. You should be careful about sharing your personal information in public spaces such as blogs, forums, socializing websites and even instant messaging services. We will not be responsible for the breach of your privacy done by third parties using the public space. 

#### Right to Collect

By registering with us you agree that we may collect and store your Personal Information subject to the declarations made in this Privacy Policy. We store your personal information to: a) manage our relationship and provide you with our services, b) make you aware of our offers, schemes and products, c) to comply with statutory requirements, and d) to customize our services and promotions as per your location, age and preferences. 

#### Exceptions

If required by law of the land and/or the security of our systems, we are bound to intercept, disclose and monitor your personal information in the manner as prescribed by law. It may happen without your knowledge.
